# **UMMEY KULSUM**

Address: House no 36, Road no-17, Nikunja - 2, Khilkhet, Dhaka

Primary Mobile No: 01711090797 Emergency Contact No: 01671019568 Primary Email : uktamanna@gmail.com



## **Career Objective:**

Obtain a good position in a dynamic organization. To work in a challenging and a fast-paced environment, make the best of my current knowledge and creativity, with learning opportunities.

### **Career Summary:**

An efficient and enthusiastic individual with 6+ years of extensive experience both in sales and public interaction environment seeking an opportunity to contribute the skills and expertise to the management team of a fast-growing company.

#### **Special Qualification:**

- Self-Motivated, organized and efficient
- Extensive experience in Customer Service
- Able to work well in high pressure environment
- Good Communication skills
- Timely Decision-Making abilities.

## **Employment History:**

Total Year of Experience: 6.9 yrs

1. Sr. Officer(3.4 yrs)

(October, 2018 - Continuing)

# NITS Service (Pvt.) Limited a sister concern of NITOL-NILOY GROUP

71 Nitol Niloy Centre, Dhaka

#### **Area of Expertise**

Generate sales lead (  $1.1~\mathrm{yrs}$  ), handle customer complain (  $1.1~\mathrm{yrs}$  ), Provide Information (  $1.1~\mathrm{yrs}$  )

#### **Duties/Responsibilities**

- Manage large amounts of incoming calls.
- Generate sales leads.
- Identify and assess customers' needs to achieve satisfaction.
- Build sustainable relationships and trust with customer accounts through open and interactive communication.
- Provide accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods/tools
- Meet personal/customer service team sales targets and call handling quotas.
- Handle customer complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limits follow up to ensure resolution.
- Keep records of customer interactions, process customer accounts and file documents.
- Follow communication procedures, guidelines and policies.
- Take the extra mile to engage customers.

# 2. Intern( 0.5 yr )

(April, 2018 - October, 2018)

## **BRAC Aarong**

B, Link Road, 346 Bijoy Sarani - Tejgaon Link Rd, Dhaka 1208

#### Area of Expertise

Administration ( 0.2 yr ), Human Resources & Development ( 0.2 yr ), Social Complaince ( 0.2 yr )

#### **Duties/Responsibilities**

- Making calls to all producers who will be audited.
- Making calls for CAD collection.
- Inform producers to collect their audit reports.
- Arrange all Video audits received and arrange them folder wise.
- · Arrange all audit reports in business file.
- Report handover to producer with CAP.
- Inform producers for producer forum.
- Inform producers for special compliance forum.
- Assist in report making.
- Assist audit unit for forum events and training sessions.
- Ad hoc field visit for audit unit.
- Make special reports which are not in business file.
- · Communicate with the auditors on behalf of the producers when audit unit is out of office.
- Updating excel files as per auditors' requirements.
- Assisting in technical works like picture resizing and editing.

### 3. Senior Trainee( 2.2 yrs )

(October, 2015 - December, 2017)

#### Grameenphone Ltd.

GPHOUSE, Basundhara R/A, Baridhara, Dhaka-1229 Bashundhara, 1229

### **Area of Expertise**

Call centre training (0.7 yr), Customer Care (0.7 yr), traning and development (0.7 yr)

#### **Duties/Responsibilities**

- Maintains customer satisfaction by providing problems-solving resources.
- Answers customers' questions.
- · Resolves problems and disseminates advisories and warnings
- Conducts surveys and forms focus groups.
- Schedules expenditures.
- Identifies customer service trends and determines system improvements
- Implements production, productivity, quality, and customer-service standards.
- Prepares and completes actions plans.
- Analyzes variance and initiates corrective actions.
- Meets customer service financial objectives by forecasting requirements.

#### 4. Sales Associate( 0.5 yr )

(April, 2015 - October, 2015)

## **BRAC Aarong**

Dhaka

#### Area of Expertise

Customer Support/ Client Service (0.2 yr), Retail Stores/ Shops (0.2 yr), Sales (0.2 yr)

# **Duties/Responsibilities**

Product Management, Product Display, Customer Service, Annual Inventory.

# **Academic Qualification:**

Exam Title	Concentration/Major	Institute	Result	Pas.Year	Duration
Masters of Business Studies(MBS)	Management	National University	First Class, Marks :61.4%	2014	1 year
Bachelor of Business Studies (BBS)	Management	National University	Second Class, Marks :52.73%	2012	4 year
Post Graduate Diploma (PGD)	Human Resource Management	Bangladesh Institute of Management (BIM)	CGPA:3.21 out of 4	2019	1 year
Post Graduate Diploma (PGD)	HR, Admin & Compliance	Bangladesh Garments Management Institute (BGMI)	pass	2018	4 months
HSC	Business Studies	Govt. Pioneer Girls College, Khulna	CGPA:4 out of 5	2005	-
SSC	Business Studies	Bashtali Secondary School, Bagerhat	CGPA:3.31 out of 5	2003	-

# **Training Summary:**

Training Title	Topic	Institute	Country	Location	Year	Duration
Enterprise Resource Planning		BRAC Aarong	Bangladesh	Aarong Khulna	2015	1 day
Point Of Sales		BRAC Aarong	Bangladesh	Aarong Khulna	2014	1 day
Customer Service Refresher		BRAC Aarong	Bangladesh	BRAC Learning Centre, KHULNA	2013	1 day
Professionalism in Customer Service		BRAC Aarong	Bangladesh	BRAC Learning Centre, KHULNA	2012	1day
Customer Service For Sales Associate		Aarong	Bangladesh	BRAC Learning Centre , KHULNA	2011	1 day

# **Professional Qualification:**

Certification	Institute	Location	From	То
Preparing to Manage Human Resources	Coursera	N/A	May 17, 2021	June 7, 2021
Organizational design Know your organization	Coursera	N/A	April 19, 2021	May 17, 2021
Customer How to Understand Customer Needs	Udemy	N/A	April 6, 2021	April 9, 2021
Learn HR Fundamentals for a Career in Human Resources	Udemy	N/A	March 23, 2021	March 29, 2021
Smart Employee Engagement for Sustainability	Udemy	N/A	March 23, 2021	March 29, 2021

# **Career and Application Information:**

Looking For : Mid Level Job Available For : Full Time

Preferred Job Category

General Management/Admin, Customer Support/Call Centre, HR/Org. Development,
Showroom Assistant/Salesman, Data Entry/Computer Operator, Graphic Designer

# **Specialization:**

### **Fields of Specialization**

- Microsoft Excel
- General HR
- HR
- Administration
- Management
- Hard Working
- Multitasking
- Ability to Work Under Pressure
- Team player

# **Language Proficiency:**

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking
Bengali	High	High	High
English	Medium	Medium	Medium

### **Personal Details:**

Father's Name : Late Sarder Jalal Uddin Mother's Name : Nurunnahar Begum Date of Birth : October 19, 1988

Gender : Female Marital Status : Married Nationality : Bangladeshi : 2823415142 National Id No.

Religion : Islam

Permanent Address : Village & Post: Bashtali, Rampal, Bagerhat

**Current Location** : Dhaka **Blood Group** : A+

# Reference (s):

Reference: 01

Name : Sheikh Sunny Mohammad Talha

Organization : Bangladesh Army

Lieutenant Colonel AAG,AHQ PA Designation

Directorate

Address : Dhaka Cantonment, Dhaka

Phone (Off.) : 01769012472

Phone (Res.)

: 01715949181 Mobile

E-Mail

Relation : Relative Reference: 02

Shuvo Kibria

Weekly News Magazine SHAPTAHIK

**Executive Editor** 

Channel I Bhaban 40 Shahid Tajuddin Ahmad

Sarani, Tejgaon I/A, Dhaka-1208

01716-410928

kibria34@gmail.com

Others